前情提要
Previously on Lost
你杀了Naomi
You killed Naomi
她想让她的人到岛上来
She want's her people to come here
相信我  我们得赶在
and trust me, when they do
他们到之前离开这儿
We had better be far away from here.
要想活命就跟我来
If you want to live,you need to come with me.
你是谁?
Who are you?
-Daniel Faraday  我是来救你们的  -就这些人吗?
Daniel faraday. I'm here to rescue you. so this is the team?
他们不合适参加这种任务
These are the wrong people for a mission like this.
无实战经验  没受过军事训练
None of them have field experience,military training.
不能置他们于危险而不顾
You can't just drop them in unprotected.
我尽力而为吧
There's only so much I can do.
直升机坠毁在哪?
Where's the chopper? where did it crash?
坠毁?  你当我菜鸟啊?
crash?what kind of pilot you think I am?
我把它好好的藏起来了  就在那儿
I put her down safe and sound right over there.
起来  跟我们走
Get up. you're coming with us. well,
我们得留在这儿  这样他们才找得到我们
we need to stay where we are so that they can find us.
你错了  我们不想被别人发现
See,there's your problem. we don't want to be found.
你想知道我为何到这来吗?
You wanted to know why we're here?
直说了吧  我们是来找Benjamin Linus的
I'll tell you why we're here. we're here for benjamin linus.
他现在在哪儿?
Now where is he?
Ben之前有提到
Did ben ever mention anything
有人离开过这岛的事情吗?
About knowing anyone off the island?
-你确定吗?  -没有
You're sure of that? no.
听着  事情很简单
Look,this is real simple.
你知不知道他在哪儿?
Do you know where he is or don't you?
-你找他干嘛?  -我想知道他的位置
What do you want with him? I wanna locate him.
我的雇主只告诉我他叫Benjamin Linus
The people who hired me told me his name's benjamin linus.
和一张照片  只告诉我这么多
They gave this picture,and that's all they told me.
只吩咐叫我找到他  然后拿钱
They said,"find him." and for what they're paying me,
其它我都不关心
I don't need to know anything else.
你知道么?
Do you?
你找Ben?
You want ben?
好吧  他和你的朋友还有Locke在一起
Okay,he's with locke and your friend...
-Charlotte  -Charlotte
Charlotte. charlotte.
Locke也抓住了她  我们知道他往哪去
Locke's got her,too,and we know where he's heading.
Locke是杀了Naomi的那厮吗?
Locke's the guy that killed naomi?
Shephard把枪还给我
Give me back my gun,shephard.
想要枪  先回答我的问题
You want your gun back. I want answers.
-你不相信我  -我不相信你
You don't trust me. I don't trust you.
其实你早该死翘翘了
In fact,you're supposed to be dead.
我之前问过什么了吗?  没有
But am I asking a billion questions? no.
我们都要面对Locke这个大麻烦
We both have the same problem-- this locke guy.
就算Locke抓了你的同伴
Even if locke has your friend,
你也不能大摇大摆地去带人走
You can't just waltz in there and grab her.
他们有武装的
They're armed.
那又怎样?  我们不也一样吗
Well,how about that? so are we.
我们快行动吧
So why don't we move out and--
你哪儿也别去  直升机还能飞吗?
You're not going anywhere. will that helicopter fly?
可以
What she does.
-那就带我去你船上  -Sayid  等等
Then you can take me to your ship. sayid,wait a second.
我们说过让他们带我们走  不是吗?
We did call these people to get us off this island, Didn't we?
怎样?
Well?
来的时候耗油太多了
I burned a lot of fuel coming in.
不能载太多重量
I can't carry much weight.
我带你们三人走
I'll take three of ya.
你这山羊胡子白日发昏吧?!
In case you zoned out while you were tweezing your goatee,
别忘了这些乡巴佬还抓了Charlotte呢
One of these yahoos took charlotte prisoner.
我能把她安全救出来
I can bring her back safely.
要是我做到了...
And if I do...
你会带我上船吗?
Will you take me to the ship?
肯定会
Absolutely.
你把Charlotte安然无恙带回来
You bring charlotte back safe,
我就带你们离开这座小岛
And I will take you off this island.
早上好
Good morning.
Morning.
距下一个洞还远呢
It's a long walk to the next hole.
要我搭你一程吗?
Do you need a ride?
谢谢  不必了  我的球就在这儿呢
Thank you,but no. my ball is right here.
知道吗,你是我见过第一个在这儿晃悠一早上的人
You know, You're the first person I've seen out here all morning.
我想大家为了彼此的私人空间
I believe we're paying quite a premium
都花了不少
For that kind of privacy.
确实是这样
Indeed we are.
第一次来Seychelles吗?
Is this your first time in the seychelles?
是我就用5号杆
Unh-unh. I'd use the 5-iron.
我想我还是用7号
I think I'll stick with the 7.
这样吧,赌50欧元,5号杆肯定打得更近
Tell you what. 50 euros says mine goes closer to the pin with a 5.
赌100吧
Let's make it 100.
好样的
Eccellente.
有意思
Amazing,huh,
还有什么能比打赌更有趣的呢?
How a wager makes just about anything more fun?
不赖啊
Not bad.
好球
说起来...
So...
你是干什么的  朋友?
What do you do for a living,my friend?
无所事事
I do nothing.
无所事事可付不起这度假费哦
"nothing" doesn't pay for a vacation here.
我是大笔赔偿款的受益者
I was the recipient of a large settlement.
公司并购吗?
Corporate merger?
准确来说是空难
Actually,a plane crash.
大洋航班815号
Oceanic airlines flight 815.
我是Sayid Jarrah
I'm sayid jarrah.
大洋6人之一
One of the oceanic six.
这...
Ah,that's...
这...  这真是奇迹
That's--that's amazing. uh...
我记得那段时间常常在报上看到这事
I remember reading all about it.
挥杆吧  朋友
Take your shot,my friend.
看起来你说用5号杆是对的
It appears you were right about the 5 iron.
您继续玩吧  赌金的事儿就算了吧
Enjoy you round,and,uh,don't worry about the wager.
玩玩而已嘛
It's all in good fun.
不  你赢了  我愿赌服输
No,you won. allow me to pay you.
没事的  谢谢你  这...
It's fine,thank you. it's...
一定得给您  Avellino先生
I insist,mr. avellino.
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：思思　多多　天龙　小帝
校对：奇奇  hailongren  小帝 许愿
字幕总监制：何何  梁良
这座位有人么?
你想去哪里?
德语我只会说一句"这座位有人么?"
"is it free?" was the full extent of my german.
你在找什么?
What are you looking for?
我爱死欧洲了  人人都会说英语
I love europe. everyone speaks english.
我在找波茨坦广场
I'm looking for potsdamer platz.
那用不着地图
Well,you don't need a map.
离这就一个街区  过街就是
It's one block down,right across the street.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是Elsa
I'm elsa.
Sayid
Sayid.
请给我来杯蒸馏咖啡
Could I have an espresso,please?
什么风把你吹到柏林来了?
What sort of business brings you to berlin?
我是来物色人才的
I'm a headhunter.
帮公司招兵买马
A corporate recruiter.
我的老板是个经济学家  他专门研究新兴的市场
My employer is an economist. he works in emerging markets.
事实上  我还真不知道他是干什么的
Actually,i-i don't really understand what he does,
这也无所谓  因为我只是帮他购物就行了
Which doesn't matter since all I do is shop for him.
这玩意一响
And if this goes off,
我就得马上出现在他面前
I'm at his side instantly,
其实这差事儿很棒 因为他一年只来柏林一两次
Which is wonderful since he's only in berlin once or twice a year.
所以你在这里享受 奢侈的午间咖啡
Which is why you're enjoying a luxuriously long midday coffee.
是啊
Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
我...
Do i...
好像在哪见过你似的
Know you from somewhere?
如果你肯跟我去吃晚饭
I'll tell you exactly where you know me from...
我就一五一十地告诉你
If you let me take you to dinner.
今晚带我去这个餐馆
This is the restaurant you're taking me to tonight.
八点
8:00.
只要你能找的到
Well... if you can find it.
喂
Hello?
已经联系上了
I made contact.
好的
Good.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
Naomi身上的
Naomi had it with her.
她在找Desmond
She was looking for desmond.
不管他们本来的企图是什么
Whatever their real agenda is,
明显他们内部的人都有事互相隐瞒
It's clear they're not sharing it.
也许Desmond能解释这一切
Maybe desmond can shed some light on this.
到海滩一去一回要多久?
How long would it take to get to the beach and back?
几个小时吧
Couple of hours.
要不你去?
You mind?
乐意帮忙
Anything I can do to help.
Sayid
Sayid.
怎么做?
So how we gonna do this?
这种行动你不合适
You're not the best candidate for this kind of mission.
这是哪种行动?
Well,and what kind of mission is that?
我去让Locke放了Charlotte
I'm going to make locke release charlotte,
而且要和平解决
And I'm going to do it without any bloodshed.
我去了就得流血吗?
As opposed to the way I'd do it?
上次你见到他
The last time you encountered him,
你用枪指着他的头  还扣了扳机
You put a gun to his head and pulled the trigger.
这方法可不够好
That's not good diplomacy.
嘿  Jarrah
Hey. jarrah.
你想去找Charlotte不带我么?
You think you're going after charlotte without me?
当然不是
Of course not.
好的
Well,good.
还有什么事吗?
Is there anything else?
有啊  把枪给我
Yeah. give me my gun back.
10分钟后出发
We leave in ten minutes.
给我们个名字吧  阴谋家
Ready to give us a name,gizmo?
James  他不会告诉你哪个是混进船上的间谍的
He's not gonna tell you who his spy is on their boat,james.
是吗?  为什么不会呢?
Yeah? why not?
因为他想活命
Because that's the only thing that's keeping him alive.
我有个主意
Well,here's an idea.
我们把枪对着他的大脚趾
Why don't we take a gun,point it to his big toe
然后拿到市场上去卖
And send that little piggy to market?
如果他还不就范
And if he still doesn't want to tell us,
我们就来烤肉  这样可以吧
We'll move on to the roast beef. now why don't we do that?
那样的话我们就得背上他了
Because then we'd have to carry him.
John  还有多远?  我要给Aaron喂奶了
Hey,john,how much further is it? i-i need to feed aaron.
应该在这啊...  那个小屋
It should be here... the cabin.
可能我们迷路了  根本不在这
Maybe we got turned around. it could be anywhere.
不  肯定是这没错
No,it was here.
屋子里有什么东西这么重要?
Well,what's in this cabin that's so important anyway?
John想从某人那儿得到下一步的指示
John's looking for somebody to tell him what to do next.
我想我弄错了
I guess I was mistaken.
这不重要
It doesn't... doesn't matter.
依计划行事  继续走  营地不远了
Plan's the same. we keep movin'. the barracks aren't far.
如果她的人和Jack在一起
If her team is with jack's group,
他们知道我们要去营地
They know we're going to the barracks.
红发女郎穿了防弹衣
Yeah,and red here was wearing a vest.
就表明她的人肯定准备跟我们火并一场
Which means her posse's gonna come Expecting themselves a gunfight.
他们要的是她  我们就放她走
if all they want is her, maybe we should just let her go.
我是说  我们干脆藏起来
I mean,i thought we were just gonna go hide.
干嘛要带着囚犯
Why do we need to take prisoners?
-因为她还有利用价值  -怎么利用她?
We're keeping her because she's gonna be valuable. how is she gonna be valuable?
他是说将我做人质  亲爱的
He means as a hostage,luv.
不  我可不是来干这个的
Unh-unh. no,this is not what I signed up for.
-那你是来干什么的  -我意思是我们...
What did you sign up for,hugo? look,i'm just saying I think we
如果放她走  他们会觉得我们有诚意
If we let her go,they'll look at it as a sign of good faith.
他们会觉得我们很愚蠢
They'll look at it as an act of foolishness, Which is what it would be.
我只是想提个妥协的建议
I'm just trying to come up with some sort of compromise
妥协是没用的
We're beyond compromise.
现在  我说了算  Hugo
And right now,hugo,i'm making the decision.
你有意见吗
Is that gonna be a problem for you?
很糟糕吧?
Kinda sucks,huh?
什么?
what's that?
Sayid让你别去
Being told not to come along.
现在你明白我的感受了
Now you know what it feels like to be me.
是不是说我该等个20分钟  再跟他们去?
Does that mean I should wait 20 minutes and ago anyway?
好笑
touch?
你应该和他们走  Kate
You should go with them,kate.
你是认真的?
you're serious?
是的
yeah.
你不信任Sayid?
What,don't you trust sayid?
我不信任Locke
I don't trust locke.
万一他对我就像他对Naomi一样怎么办?
So what's preventing him from doing to me what he did to naomi?
Sawyer不会让他这么干的
Sawyer won't let him.
还有我的位子吗
Got room for one more?
她有枪
Oh,yeah,she gets a gun.
万不得已才用枪
The gun's a last resort,kate
你也是这么对Locke说的?
You give locke that same speech?
我们出发吧
Hey! let's move out.
那个叫Sayid的  他是哪儿的人
This guy sayid-- where's he from?
伊拉克
iraq.
伊拉克?
他能处理好这些事?
So he's just gonna go and work everything out?
他是干嘛的  外交官?
What was he,a diplomat?
不
No
他是个拷问官
He was a torturer.
Naomi  你们是朋友吗?
Naomi-- were you close to her?
不  上了船才认识的
Nope. met her on the boat.
看来你对她的死没什么感觉
You don't seem particularly affected by her death.
不  我有感觉  她身材很辣  我替她感到惋惜
Sure I'm affected. she was hot,and I dug her accent.
真不错
nice.
而这个叫Charlotte的
And this woman--charlotte.
你也不太关心她  是不
You don't really care about her,do you?
怎么才算关心?
define "care."
朋友间的感情
So much for camaraderie.
对  谁是才是带枪追捕
Yeah,gee,who's the one going after
共同落难的朋友的人?
One of their crash buddies with guns?
事实上  我更关心Locke
Actually,i do care about locke.
也许你能告诉我
Maybe you can tell me
他是怎样让你们起内讧的
How he managed to split your happy little family in half.
我们为了你们
There was a fundamental debate
是来杀我们还是救我们
As to whether your people were coming to rescue us
而起了分歧
or kill us.
那你是哪一派?
And which side did you land on?
我决定了就告诉你
I'll let you know when I decide.
你很英俊
You look fantastic.
所以我才要带你去剧院
This is why I wanted to take you to the opera.
第五次约会还不能穿礼服  那就没必要约会了
If a man can't wear his tuxedo by the fifth date,why bother?
你知道吗
you know what?
我不会带着
I'm not bringing it.
如果他呼我了
If tonight's the night he calls,
就让他去吧
so be it.
我帮你带着
i'll carry it.
如果他真的呼了  我不想你怪罪我
If he does call,i don't want you fired over me.
你该跟他说  现在有更先进的
You should tell your employer that there is newer technology.
我试过了  可他很保守
Well,i've tried. he's very old-fashioned.
你知道老板都这样
You know how bosses can be.
你有老板吗
Do you have a boss?
人人都有上司  Elsa
Everyone has a boss,elsa.
走吧  别迟到了
Come on. we don't want to be late.
你怎么还在柏林
Why are you still here?
我们初次见面时,你说你只在这待一周
I mean,when we met, you said you would only be in berlin for one week.
工作的进度比我想象的要慢
The job I'm on is proving harder to accomplish than I thought.
噢
oh.
是这样
right.
真希望是因为我的缘故
I was hoping it was because of me.
走吧
Let's go.
Strauss在等着呢
Strauss awaits.
他是什么人?
What's his story?
-Daniel?  -说不清
Daniel? ah,couldn't tell you.
他跟我说的  我都是左耳进
Half the stuff he says is way over my head.
右耳出
The other half goes way,way over.
Frank  我能...  不好意思打扰了
Hey,uh,frank? can i,uh-- ooh. sorry to interrupt.
-我可以用一下电话吗?  -为什么?
May I please use the phone just for a second? for what?
我只想给船上的Regina打个电话
I just wanna call regina on the boat,
我想既然我们在等待
Cause I figure since we're waiting,
-也许我可以...  你知道...  -是怎么回事  Daniel?
Maybe I could just,you know,try to-- what is it,daniel?
我只是想试验一下  只是...
I'd just like to do an experiment. just--just a--
好吧  你就保管那个高科技的玩意  好吗?
Okay. you just keep it to that science stuff,all right? yeah.
一旦Minkowski打过来  你就立即挂掉它
If minkowski gets on there, you hang up right away.
好的  谢谢
yeah. thank you.
Regina  我是Dan  等下
Regina? hey--hi,it's dan. hang on.
能听到我吗  -是的
Can you hear me? yeah.
-是  -好的  别挂
Yeah? okay. hang on.
我这里...
I'm,uh,all... yes.
我设置好了
I am all set here.
位置固定  你能锁定吗
I have a fix. are you locked in?
你的信号很清晰
Getting your signal pretty clear.
太好了  那么...
Oh. okay,great. then... okay.
发射弹头吧
Fire the payload.
已经发射
Payload away!
别紧张,他在船上一直都在搞那些玩意儿
Don't sweat it.He does this kind of stuff on the boat all the time.
离信号源还有40公里
40 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有35公里
35 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有30公里
30 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有25公里
25 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有20公里
20 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有15公里
15 kilometers to beacon.
离信号源还有10公里
10 kilometers to beacon.
Regina
Regina?
离信号源还有5公里
5 kilometers to beacon.
零
Zero
我没看到
I don't have it.
这太怪了
That's... weird.
这可不光是奇怪
That is far more than weird.
那些秋千是做啥的?  他们还有托儿所?
What's with the swing set? these people have day care?
你觉得他们到了吗?
You think they're here yet?
过去看看吧
Let's find out.
在那边
It's coming from in there.
放我出去  救救我
Let me go! help me!
Hurley  怎么回事
Hurley,what happened?
他们把我撇下了
They left me.
Locke背离了原先的约定
Locke's gone off the reservation,man.
我是说  他带走了那个小妞
I mean,he took this one chick hostage,
他说是Walt叫他杀了Naomi的
He said walt was the one Who told him to kill the other chick,and he
Walt?
walt?
伙计  别问了  我只是想和他辩论一下
Dude,don't ask. I was,like,just trying to argue with him
但是他就变脸了  但是
So he would just,like,you know,chill,but,
你能不能别唠里唠叨
uh-- how about you stop babbling,
-就告诉我们他们怎么了  他们在哪里?
Just tell us what happened to them? where are they?
-你是谁?  -他们去哪里了?  胖子
Who are you?Where the hell did they go,tubby?
太可怕了,这条船又给我们送来一个Sawyer
Oh,awesome. the ship sent us another sawyer.
Hurley  他们去哪儿了?
Hurley,where did they go?
我想他们光顾着绑我忘记给我说了
L-look,i guess they were too busy tying me up to tell me.
-我不知道  -因此他们全都走了
I don't know. and so they all left,all together?
对  他们很反常  Locke说船上的人
Yeah,they were freaked. locke said that the people on the ship
是来救Charlotte然后就会杀了我们
Were coming to rescue charlotte and then to kill us.
是这样吗
So... are you?
至少现在不是
Not yet.
他们提到过什么可以看出他们去哪儿了吗
Did they say anything that suggested where they were going next?
Locke说过他们
Uh,locke said they were
在离开以前会路过Ben的那所房子
Gonna go by ben's house before they took off.
-为啥他要去那里?  -就我所知
Why would he go there? for all I know,
-他们也把Ben给关在橱子里了  -Ben的房子在哪儿
They could've locked ben up in the closet,too. where's ben's house?
介意我请教你个问题吗?
Mind if I ask you a question?
但讲无妨
Shoot.
波士顿红袜队拿到了总冠军?
The red sox really win the series?
别惹我谈那个话题  好吗
Hey,don't get me started on that,all right?
我爸爸来自纽约布朗克斯  我热爱洋基队
My dad's from the bronx. I bleed yankee blue.
真不敢相信,上百天没看球赛了
I can't believe.It's been a hundred days since I've seen a game.
那是弹头
It's the payload.
终于到了
It's finally here.
那是什么
What is that?
是个火箭
It's a rocket.
不不
Oh,no.
大事不妙
This is not good.
你的朋友们回来了
Your friends are back.
瞧啊
Look at that.
看能否找到显示他们去处的痕迹
Look for anything that might show where they've gone.
我从这里找
I'll start in here.
Sayid!
别担心  Kate没事
Don't worry. kate's fine.
干得好  Hugo
Good job,hugo.
抱歉  伙计
Sorry,dude.
很抱歉  Sayid  我不是针对你
I'm sorry,sayid. nothing personal.
Locke在哪？
Where's locke?
正跟那个生气的中国人说话
Talking to that angry chinese guy.
我不会伤害你的  Hurley
I'm not going to hurt you,hurley.
是吗...我见过你象跳霹雳舞一样
Yeah... I saw you snap that guy's neck
用腿扭断了那人的脖子
With that break-dancing thing you do with your legs.
我可得掂量着点
I think I'll hang back here.
那么...
Well...
我猜他们逃出了监狱
I guess they're running out of jail space
你知道  我已经输了一块钱了
I lost a dollar,you know.
怎么输的?
How'd you manage that?
我和John打赌你不会蠢到
I bet john that you wouldn't be stupid enough
为了朋友  像个诱饵似的被捕
To fall for your friend as bait.
你了解友谊?
What do you know about friendship?
我知道有个自己不信任的朋友是没用的
I know it's no use having friends you can't trust.
我是你的囚犯了?
So what I'm your prisoner?
如果那么说能让你好受些的话
If that sorta thing turns you on.
你和Locke混在一起干嘛
What are you doing here with locke?
-我没和他一起  -你就是  James
I'm not with him. yeah,you are,james.
-那你跟Jack在一起干嘛  -我和他一道  是因为我相信
Then what are you doing with jack? I went with jack because I believe
他能把我们带出岛
He can get us off this island.
我想这就是我们的区别所在
Then I guess that's the difference between us.
我没想着要走
I ain't lookin' to leave.
为什么不
Why not?
因为回去对我已经没什么意义了
Cause I ain't got nothin' back there for me.
那在这有什么好?
And what's here that's so much better?
你又为什么要回去  Kate?
Why do you wanna go back,kate?
那应该只会让你想起我们来这之前
Seem to recall you being shuttled off to jail
你被关在监狱的日子
Before we landed here.
如果你认为除了手铐还有什么别的
So if you think there's anything waitin' for you back home
在等你回去的话
Other than handcuffs,
那你真是不清楚这个世界是什么样的
Then you really don't know how the world works.
看看周围  雀斑女
Look around us,freckles.
我们有房屋...
We got roofs over our heads...
有电  淋浴  床
Electricity,showers,beds.
多久  Sawyer?
How long,sawyer?
你觉得我们玩多久过家家?
How long do you think we can play house?
让我们拭目以待
Why don't we find out?
冰茶
Iced tea.
我觉得你可能口渴了
I thought you might be thirsty.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
骗了你我很抱歉
I'm sorry about all the theatrics,
但是  我不知道你们会有多少人
But,uh,i didn't know how many of you there would be
也不知道你们有没有武器
Or whether you'd be armed.
我必须得...  保住自己
I had to... cover my bases.
你把Miles和Kate怎么了?
What have you done with miles and kate?
Kate跟Sawyer在一起  Miles在别的地方
Kate's with sawyer,and miles is somewhere else.
他很好  我只不过问了他一些问题
He's fine. all I did was ask him some questions.
他回答了吗  -没有
Did he answer any? no.
你们抓的那个女人有没有说些什么?
Did you have more luck with the woman you captured?
没什么有用的
Not particularly.
-那么把她交给我吧  -我为什么要那么做?
Then why don't you turn her over to me? and why would I do that?
我同意这些人是群骗子
I agree that these people are liars.
他们来这也不是为了救我们
And they're certainly not here to rescue us.
但如果我把Charlotte完好地交给他们
But if I return safely with charlotte,
他们会让我一起上船
They'll take me to their ship.
这将会是我们找出它们真实身份
It's our best chance at finding out who they are
和意图的最好方法
And what they really want.
我能省去你这些麻烦  Sayid
Well,then,i can save you a lot of trouble,sayid,
因为Ben说有一个他的间谍在船上
Because ben says he's got a spy on the boat.
谁?
Who?
保密
It's a secret.
对不起,不过相信他就是出卖灵魂
Forgive me,but the day I start trusting him Is the day I would have sold my soul.
把Charlotte交给我
Give me charlotte,
允许我用自己的方式做事
Allow me to do things my way,
否则纷争一旦开始就不是我们能控制的了
Or a war is coming which we will both be powerless to stop.
我为什么要把Charlotte白白给你?
Why would I give you charlotte for nothing?
你误会了
Oh,i think you misunderstood me.
我没想让你把她白白交给我
I never expected you to give her to me for nothing.
穿衣服吧?
Should we get dressed?
不
No
我们总得在什么时候
Well  we're gonna have to get out of this bed
离开这张床吧
At a certain point
为什么?
Why?
为了这个
Well,for one thing,
因为我知道最终
Because I know that eventually
你必须要去工作
You're gonna have to go to that job of yours.
你知道  就是那个你从不肯谈起的工作
You know,the one you never talk about.
没什么可说的  就是份工作而已
There's nothing to talk about. it's just a job.
我对你一无所知
I know nothing about you.
我理解你不想谈那次坠机
I understand you don't want to talk about the crash,
你遭遇了什么?
What happened to you.
但现在的生活怎么样
But what about life now?
现在的你又如何?
What about you?
你就是这样谈恋爱的  对吧?
That's what you do when you're in love,right?
谈恋爱?
In love?
是啊
Yeah.
好
Okay.
我都实话说了吧
No more secrets.
你想知道些什么?
What do you want to know?
是他...
He's here...
我老板
My boss.
我...
I,uh...
-我要走了 -现在?
I have to go. now?
去哪?
Where?
Adlon 宾馆
Hotel adlon.
我的衣服呢
Where's my dress?
Elsa?
你必须得离开Berlin
You have to leave berlin.
什么
What?
你不能再呆在这儿了
You can't be here anymore.
你是什么意思  我不能...
What do you mean? why would i--
人们会马上疑问
People will be asking questions soon
你的老板发生了什么事
About what happened to your employer.
而你不能在这回答他们的问题
And you can't be around to answer them.
我的老板?
My employer?
这...  这是关于我的老板的?
This... this is about my boss?
你到底是谁
Who are you?
-这无关紧要  -在咖啡厅...
It has nothing to do with how-- the cafe...
你故意接近我?
You meant to meet me there?
你利用我来接近我的老板?
You used me to get to my boss?
你刚刚说什么  人们会问他发生了什么事
What did you say--people will ask what happened to him?
最好你不知道
it's best you don't know.
你要去杀他吗
Are you gonna kill him?
你真的要去杀他吗
You're gonna kill him?
你和他又素不相识
Do you even know him?
他在名单之列
His name is on a list.
-名单?  什么名单?  你有一份名单?  -我老板的
A list?! what list? you--you have a list? my employer's.
-你老板是谁  -他是谁不重要
Who is that? it doesn't matter who he is!
你杀人就因为他在名单上吗? 那无辜的人呢？
So you just kill people 'cause they're on a list?Innocent people?
你的老板并不是经济学家
The man you are working for is not an economist.
你打算十点半和我见面吗？
You were supposed to page me at ten-thirty.
我还没有杀他
No, I didn't kill him.
他不打算放弃那份名单
He's not going to give up the name now.
为什么不杀他？
Why should I keep him alive?
不  他不知道
No. He had no idea.
好的  好的
All right, all right.
我会带他到你那去的
I'll bring him to you.
离开旅馆
Leave the hotel.
安全屋见
I'll meet you at the safe house.
你以为你...
What do you think you're--
我最后问你一次
Hey,i'm gonna ask you one last time.
为什么Naomi带着我的照片
Why was naomi carrying this picture of me?
伙计  要知道
Look,man,you gotta understand something.
她是我的上司
She was senior management.
我们并不一起做事
It's not like we hung around the cafeteria together.
-她一向单枪匹马  -Naomi告诉过我你们受雇于她
She stayed on her own-- look, naomi told me you people were hired by her.
看着我的双眼
So you look me right in the eye
告诉我你从来没有见过和听说过Penelope Widmore
And tell me you've never seen or heard of penelope widmore.
好吧,你不想告诉我真相
Fine. You don't want to tell me the truth?
我会去找别人
I'll find someone who will.
明白吗  飞机起飞时  我也要在上面
See,when that takes off,i'm on it.
他回来了
He's back.
Kate在哪里
Where's kate?
她决定留下来
She decided to stay.
Miles怎么了
What happened to miles?
-我做了交易  -交换?
I traded him. traded him?
我保证过把Charlotte带来  她现在来了
I promised you charlotte. here she is.
你作弊了
You cheated.
-是吗  -是的
Did i? yes,you did.
你真幸运  这家伙对我来说是个讨厌鬼
Lucky for you,that guy's nothing but a pain in my ass.
你还好吗
You all right?
好了  这样多了一个空位
All right,that gives us room for one more.
你走吗  Charlotte
Charlotte?
我在这儿很开心啊
Go back,with all the fun I'm having here?
不是  我在这儿还有工作
No. I've got work to do.
Daniel  如果你想的话就跟我们走
Seat's your if you want it,daniel.
我  不想走  谢谢
I--no,thank you.
我想我应该和Charlotte呆在一起
I think I should probably just stay with charlotte.
那好吧
All right.
嘿  Frank
Hey,frank.
Frank？
Frank?
就...就一件事情
Just--just... just one thing.
一定确保
Just be sure
你们一定
That you follow
要走我们来的方向  好吗
The same exact bearing that we came in on,okay?
不管发生什么
No matter what.
只有那样  我意思是不管怎么就保持那个航线
By that,i mean no matter what. just... stay on it.
知道了
Roger that.
好的
Okay.
小心点
Be careful.
我不必说服你和我们一起走
I don't have to talk you out of coming.
我其实很喜欢坐直升机... 我想你很会用这个
As much as I like helicopter rides, I think you got this one under control.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Good luck.
给我寄明信片
Send me a postcard.
你说我们还有多的空位？
You said we have room for one more?
是的  怎么？
Yeah. why?
你应该带Naomi回家
You should bring naomi home.
脱下你的衣服
Take your shirt off.
她死了吗
Is she dead?
是的
Yes.
她为什么没有杀你
Why didn't she kill you?
她试图从我这儿套信息
She was trying to get information from me.
什么信息
What sort of information?
她想知道我为谁工作
She wanted to know who I worked for.
她想知道你
She wanted to know about you.
她当然想知道
Of course she did.
你哭是因为痛吗
Are you crying because it hurts,
还是你傻到真的关心她?
Or because you were stupid enough to care for her?
这些人不值得我们的同情
These people don't deserve our sympathies.
需要我来提醒你吗?
Need I remind you what they did
上次你就过于仁慈
The last time you thought with your heart instead of your gun?
你也用这招诱使我为你杀人
You used that to recruit me to killing for you.
你还想不想保护你的朋友  Sayid?
Do you wanna protect your friends or not,sayid?
我告诉你下一个目标的名字
I have another name for you.
可他们已经注意到我了
But they know I'm after them now.
很好
Good.